DANI RAMDANI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

081271400716 | ddaniramdani10@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/dani-ramdani10 | porto-daisyui.vercel.app

Jakarta, Indonesia

A bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering from Kuningan University. Experienced as a Front-End Developer who works with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js and Node.js. Attending Full-Stack Web Developer Bootcamp program for deepening skills in Web Developer. A detail-oriented individual who is eager for a full-time opportunity in Full-Stack Web Development.

Work Experience

Roomfazza - Kuningan, Indonesia

Feb, 2018 - Present

Social Media Specialist

- Make plans to advertise product sales
- · Create content for social media and advertising needs
- Scheduling content uploads to social media

Project Experiences

Anime List - Self Project

Nov, 2023 - Present

Front-End Developer

- Developing online streaming anime using Nextis and Tailwind CSS
- Consume Jikan API for anime data sources

Portfolio Website - Self Project

Sep, 2023 - Oct, 2023

Front-End Developer

- Created Single pages for a personal portfolio website
- Designed a portfolio website using ReactJs and Tailwind to speed up website development

Kasir app - Self Project

Jul, 2023 - Sep, 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- Created a web application to handle a large number of customer orders
- Used Bootstrap and ReactJs are used to build the user interface

Organization Experiences

Informatics Engineering Student Seminar - Kuningan, Indonesia

Created detailed and specific concepts and event arrangements

Mar, 2022 - Apr, 2023

- Be a Smart User with Your Smartphone Become a Smart Entrepreneur
- Organized and led all related activities with events

Education Level

Kuningan University - Kuningan, Indonesia

2015 - 2020

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.47/4.00

- Thesis: The Virtual Reality-Based Shortest Path Searching Application For Existing Building Locations In Kuningan University Using Dijkstra Algorithm.
- Relevant Course Works: Algorithm, Virtual Reality, Java, Unity.

Courses, Training and Certifications

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Nov, 2023 - Feb, 2024

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp, 3.54/4.00

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for an insurance company, Insurance Technology, within three months
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Native and Node.js
- Certificate:

Revo-U - Jakarta, Indonesia

Jul, 2023 - Jul, 2023

Fundamental Course – Intro to Software Engineering

- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Certificate: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1qGAaOvN8iMazHD6Wi0HzUhkSZ17wWcle/view

Skills

Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Node.js, React js, PHP,GIT and Figma

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Time Management and Teamwork

Languages: English (Intermediate), Indonesian (Native)